A Guide to the Robert N. Giaimo Papers 1980.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series III: Legislative Correspondence, 1973-1981
  - 95th Congress, 1st Session, 1977 (Box not specified)
    - Social Security
      - Railroad Retirement Benefits (Box 42:, Folder 1629)
      - Spouses Benefits (Box 42:, Folder 1630)
    - Taxation
      - General (Box 43:, Folder 1631)
      - Corporations and Special Interests (Box 43:, Folder 1632)
      - Income Tax-Individual (Box 43:, Folder 1633-1636)
      - Reform (Box 43:, Folder 1637)
    - Transportation
      - General (Box 43:, Folder 1638)
      - Aviation (Box 43:, Folder 1639)
      - Buses and Trucks (Box 43:, Folder 1640)
      - Highways (Box 43:, Folder 1641)
      - Mass Transit (Box 43:, Folder 1642)
      - No-Fault Insurance (Box 43:, Folder 1643)
      - Railroads (Box 43:, Folder 1644-1650)
      - Shipping and Merchant Marine (Box 43:, Folder 1651)
    - Veterans
      - General (Box 43:, Folder 1652)
      - Disability (Box 43:, Folder 1653)
      - Education (Box 43:, Folder 1654)
      - Health (Box 43:, Folder 1655)
    - Veterans
      - Pensions (Box 43:, Folder 1656)
  - 95th Congress, 2nd Session, 1978
    - General Legislation (Box not specified)
      - State Matter/No Jurisdiction (Box 44:, Folder 1657)
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 44:, Folder 1658)
    - Animal Protection
      - Land (Box 44:, Folder 1659)
      - Water (Box 44:, Folder 1660-1661)
    - Arts and Humanities
      - General (Box 44:, Folder 1662)
    - Business
      - General (Box 44:, Folder 1663)
      - Independent Business Ballots (Box 44:, Folder 1664)
      - Banking and Finance (Box 44:, Folder 1665-1667)
      - Product Liabilities (Box 44:, Folder 1668)
      - Small Business (Box 44:, Folder 1669)
    - Civil Rights and Liberties
      - General (Box 44:, Folder 1670)
      - Indian Affairs (Box 44:, Folder 1671)
      - School Busing (Box 44:, Folder 1672)
      - School Prayer (Box 44:, Folder 1673)
      - Women's Rights (Box 44:, Folder 1674-1675)
    - Consumers
      - General (Box 44:, Folder 1676)
      - CATV (Box 44:, Folder 1677)
      - Consumer Protection Legislation (Box 44:, Folder 1678-1679)
      - Copyrights-Patents (Box 44:, Folder 1680)
      - Privacy (Box 44:, Folder 1681)
      - Postal Service (Box 44:, Folder 1682)
    - Economy
      - General (Box 44:, Folder 1683)
      - Connecticut and New Haven (Box 44:, Folder 1684)
      - Federal Spending (Box 44:, Folder 1685-1686)
      - Minimum Wage (Box 44:, Folder 1687)
      - Newsletter, Federal Spending (Box 44:, Folder 1688)
      - New York Loan (Box 44:, Folder 1689)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 44:, Folder 1690)
      - Unemployment/Inflation (Box 44:, Folder 1691)
    - Education (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 45:, Folder 1692-1693)
      - Elementary and Secondary Education (Box 45:, Folder 1694)
    - Education
      - Higher Education (Box 45:, Folder 1695)
      - Libraries/Support Services (Box 45:, Folder 1696)
      - School Lunch (Box 45:, Folder 1697-1698)
      - Vocational and Adult (Box 45:, Folder 1699)
    - Energy
      - General (Box 45:, Folder 1700-1701)
      - National Energy Act (Box 45:, Folder 1702)
      - New England Energy Caucus (Box 45:, Folder 1703)
      - Northeast (Econo) (Box 45:, Folder 1704-1706)
      - Nuclear (Box 45:, Folder 1707)
      - Oil and Gasoline (Box 45:, Folder 1708)
      - Research and Development (Box 45:, Folder 1709)
      - Solar/Geothermal (Box 45:, Folder 1710)
    - Environment
      - General (Box 45:, Folder 1711)
      - Emission Control/Auto Pollution (Box 45:, Folder 1712)
      - Land Protection and Use (Box 45:, Folder 1713)
      - National Parks and Forests (Box 45:, Folder 1714)
      - Recycling (Box 45:, Folder 1715)
      - Water Pollution (Box 45:, Folder 1716)
    - Foreign Affairs
      - General (Box 45:, Folder 1717)
      - Africa (Box 45:, Folder 1718)
      - Asia (Box 45:, Folder 1719)
      - Europe and NATO (Box 45:, Folder 1720-1722)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 45:, Folder 1723)
      - International Trade (Box not specified)
        - General (Box 46:, Folder 1724-1727)
        - Specialty Steel (Box 46:, Folder 1728-1730)
      - Latin America (Box 46:, Folder 1731-1734)
      - Middle East (Box 46:, Folder 1735-1738)
      - Soviet Union and Eastern Europe (Box 46:, Folder 1739-1740)
      - United Nations (Box 46:, Folder 1741)
    - General Government
      - General (Box 46:, Folder 1742-1745)
      - ATT Bill (Box 46:, Folder 1746)
      - Campaign Financing and Reform (Box 47:, Folder 1747)
      - Commemorative Stamps (Box 47:, Folder 1748)
      - Communications (Box 47:, Folder 1749)
      - Immigration Law (Box 47:, Folder 1750)
      - Issue Analysis (Box 47:, Folder 1751)
      - Private Pensions (Box 47:, Folder 1752)
    - General Government
      - Public Employees (Box 47:, Folder 1753-1754)
      - Public works (Box 47:, Folder 1755)
      - Questionnaires (Box 47:, Folder 1756-1757)
      - Regulatory Reform (Box 47:, Folder 1758)
      - Reorganization (Box 47:, Folder 1759)
      - Stockpile (Box 47:, Folder 1760)
      - Tri-State Planning Commission (Box 47:, Folder 1761)
    - Health and Safety
      - General (Box 47:, Folder 1762-1763)
      - Abortion (Box 47:, Folder 1764)
      - Diseases (Box 47:, Folder 1765)
      - Doctor's Medical Liability (Box 47:, Folder 1766)
      - Drug and Food Labeling (Box 47:, Folder 1767)
      - Hospitals and Nursing Homes (Box 47:, Folder 1768)
      - Narcotics (Box 47:, Folder 1769)
      - National Health Insurance (Box 47:, Folder 1770)
      - Health Manpower (Box 47:, Folder 1771)
      - Rehabilitation (Box 47:, Folder 1772)
      - Veterinary (Box 47:, Folder 1773)
    - House of Representatives/General
      - General (Box 47:, Folder 1774)
      - Accomplishments (Box 47:, Folder 1775)
      - Pay Raise (Box 47:, Folder 1776)
    - House of Representatives/In-House
      - Accounts and Benefits (Box 47:, Folder 1777)
      - Administrative Review (Box 47:, Folder 1778)
      - Ball Bearing Caucus (Box 47:, Folder 1779)
      - Clearinghouse on the Future (Box 47:, Folder 1780)
      - Committee on Information Systems (Box 47:, Folder 1781)
      - Democratic Caucus, General (Box 47:, Folder 1782)
      - Democratic Steering and Policy Committee (Box 47:, Folder 1783)
      - Democratic Study Group (Box 47:, Folder 1784)
      - Democratic Whip System (Box 47:, Folder 1785)
      - Diggs (Box 47:, Folder 1786)
      - Environmental Study (Box 47:, Folder 1787)
      - Ethics (Box 47:, Folder 1788)
      - Flood (Box 47:, Folder 1789)
      - House Rules (Box 47:, Folder 1790)
      - Irish Caucus (Box 47:, Folder 1791)
      - Issue Cards (Box 47:, Folder 1792)
      - Korean Lobbying (Box 47:, Folder 1793-1794)
      - Members of Congress for Peace Through Law (Box 47:, Folder 1795)
    - House of Representatives/In-House
      - Miscellaneous Caucus (Box 47:, Folder 1796)
      - New England
        - Caucus (Box 47:, Folder 1797)
        - Regional Commission (Box 47:, Folder 1798)
      - Newsletter (Box 47:, Folder 1799)
      - Northeast-Midwest Economic Coalition (Box 47:, Folder 1800-1802)
      - Port Caucus (Box 47:, Folder 1803)
      - Reform (Box 47:, Folder 1804)
      - Senate (Box 47:, Folder 1805)
      - Steel Caucus (Box 47:, Folder 1806-1807)
      - Whip Notice (Box 47:, Folder 1808)
    - Housing and Urban Problems
      - General (Box 47:, Folder 1809)
      - Community Development Act (Box 47:, Folder 1810)
      - Urban Policy Plan (Box 47:, Folder 1811-1812)
    - Judiciary
      - General (Box 47:, Folder 1813-1814)
      - Capital Punishment (Box 47:, Folder 1815)
      - Connecticut District Judgeship (Box 47:, Folder 1816-1817)
      - Court Reform (Box 47:, Folder 1818)
      - Criminal Laws (Box 49:, Folder 1819)
      - Gun Control (Box 49:, Folder 1820-1821)
      - LEAA (Box 49:, Folder 1822)
    - Labor
      - General (Box 49:, Folder 1823-1824)
      - Full Employment Bill (Box 49:, Folder 1825)
      - Illegal Aliens (Box 49:, Folder 1826)
      - Labor/Legislative Attitudes (Box 49:, Folder 1827)
      - Manpower (Box 49:, Folder 1828)
      - OSHA (Box 49:, Folder 1829)
      - Postal Workers (Box 49:, Folder 1830)
      - Retirement (Box 49:, Folder 1831)
      - Right to Work (Box 49:, Folder 1832)
      - Unemployment Compensation (Box 49:, Folder 1833)
    - Lobbyists/Pressure Groups
      - General (Box 49:, Folder 1834)
      - American Conservative Union (Box 49:, Folder 1835)
      - Americans for Democratic Action (Box 49:, Folder 1836)
      - American Monitor Poll (Box 49:, Folder 1837)
      - American Security Council (Box 49:, Folder 1838)
      - Business Groups (Box 49:, Folder 1839)
      - Capitol Hill Women's Political Caucus (Box 49:, Folder 1840)
    - Lobbyists/Pressure Groups
      - Common Cause (Box 49:, Folder 1841)
      - Congress Watch (Box 49:, Folder 1842)
      - Congressional Management Foundation (Box 49:, Folder 1843)
      - Consumer Groups (Box 49:, Folder 1844)
      - Labor Groups (Box 49:, Folder 1845)
      - League of Women Voters (Box 49:, Folder 1846)
      - Liberty Lobby (Box 49:, Folder 1847)
      - National Association of Manufacturers (Box 49:, Folder 1848)
      - Right to Win Organization (Box 49:, Folder 1849)
      - U.S. Labor Party (Box 49:, Folder 1850)
    - Poverty Programs
      - General (Box 49:, Folder 1851)
      - Food Stamps (Box 49:, Folder 1852)
      - Social Service (Box 49:, Folder 1853)
      - Welfare Reform (Box 49:, Folder 1854)
    - Social Security
      - Benefit Insurance (Box 49:, Folder 1855)
      - Disability (Box 49:, Folder 1856)
      - Eligibility (Box 49:, Folder 1857)
      - Medicaid-Medicare (Box 49:, Folder 1858)
      - Older Americans Program (Box 49:, Folder 1859)
      - Payroll Tax (Box 49:, Folder 1860)
      - Railroad Retirement Benefits (Box 49:, Folder 1861)
      - Social Security Tax Reduction (Box 49:, Folder 1862)
      - Spouses Benefits (Box 49:, Folder 1863)
    - Taxation (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 50:, Folder 1864)
      - Capital Gains (Box 50:, Folder 1865-1866)
      - Corporations and Special Interests (Box 50:, Folder 1867-1868)
      - Income Tax-Individual (Box 50:, Folder 1869-1873)
      - Proposition 13 (Box 50:, Folder 1874-1875)
      - Reform (Box 50:, Folder 1876-1879)
      - Tuition Tax Credit (Box 50:, Folder 1880-1882)
    - Transportation
      - General (Box 50:, Folder 1883)
      - Aviation (Box 50:, Folder 1884)
      - Buses and Trucks (Box 50:, Folder 1885)
      - Giaimo Amendment (Box 50:, Folder 1886)
      - Highways (Box 50:, Folder 1887-1889)
      - Merchant Marine and Shipping (Box 50:, Folder 1890)
      - Mass Transit (Box 50:, Folder 1891)
      - No-Fault Insurance (Box 50:, Folder 1892)
    - Transportation (Box not specified)
      - Railroads (Box 51:, Folder 1893-1904)
    - Veterans
      - General (Box 51:, Folder 1905)
      - Disability (Box 51:, Folder 1906)
      - Education (Box 51:, Folder 1907)
      - Health (Box 51:, Folder 1908)
      - Pensions (Box 51:, Folder 1909)
    - Standard Mail Mimeographs
      - 1977 January - June (Box 51:, Folder 1910-1918)
      - 1977 June - 1978 March (Box 52:, Folder 1919-1944)
      - 1978 March - June (Box 53:, Folder 1945-1988)
      - 1978 July - December (Box 54:, Folder 1989-2026)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, 1979 (Box not specified)
    - General Legislation
      - State Matter/No Jurisdiction (Box 55:, Folder 2027)
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 55:, Folder 2028)
    - Arts and Humanities (Box 55:, Folder 2029)
    - Business
      - General (Box 55:, Folder 2030)
      - Banking and Finance (Box 55:, Folder 2031-2032)
      - Business Legislative Attitudes (Box 55:, Folder 2033)
      - Chrysler (Box 55:, Folder 2034)
      - Independent Business Ballots (Box 55:, Folder 2035)
      - Product Liability (Box 55:, Folder 2036)
      - Small Business (Box 55:, Folder 2037)
    - Civil Rights and Liberties
      - General (Box 55:, Folder 2038)
      - Indian Affairs (Box 55:, Folder 2039)
      - School Busing (Box 55:, Folder 2040)
      - School Prayer (Box 55:, Folder 2041)
      - Women's Rights (Box 55:, Folder 2042-2043)
    - Consumers
      - General (Box 55:, Folder 2044-2045)
      - CATV (Box 55:, Folder 2046)
      - Consumer Protection Legislation (Box 55:, Folder 2047)
      - Copyrights-Patents (Box 55:, Folder 2048)
      - Privacy (Box 55:, Folder 2049)
    - Economy
      - General (Box 55:, Folder 2050-2051)
      - Connecticut and New Haven (Box 56:, Folder 2052)
      - Federal Spending (Box 56:, Folder 2053)
    - Economy
      - Minimum wage (Box 56:, Folder 2054)
      - Revenue Spending (Box 56:, Folder 2055)
      - Unemployment (Box 56:, Folder 2056)
      - Balanced Budget (Box 56:, Folder 2057)
      - Debt Ceiling (Box 56:, Folder 2058)
    - Education
      - General (Box 56:, Folder 2059-2060)
      - ESEA (Box 56:, Folder 2061)
      - Higher Education (Box 56:, Folder 2062)
      - Libraries/Support Services (Box 56:, Folder 2063)
      - Nutrition Programs (Box 56:, Folder 2064)
      - Vocational and Adult (Box 56:, Folder 2065)
    - Energy
      - General (Box 56:, Folder 2066-2068)
      - Natural Gas (Box 56:, Folder 2069)
      - Nuclear (Box 56:, Folder 2070-2071)
      - Oil and Gasoline (Box 56:, Folder 2072-2075)
      - Research and Development (Box 57:, Folder 2076)
      - Geothermal (Box 57:, Folder 2077)
    - Environment
      - General (Box 57:, Folder 2078)
      - Air Pollution (Box 57:, Folder 2079)
      - Land Protection and Use (Box 57:, Folder 2080)
      - National Parks and Forests (Box 57:, Folder 2081)
      - Recycling (Box 57:, Folder 2082)
      - Water Pollution (Box 57:, Folder 2083)
    - Foreign Affairs
      - General (Box 57:, Folder 2084)
      - Africa (Box 57:, Folder 2085)
      - Asia (Box 57:, Folder 2086-2087)
      - Europe and NATO (Box 57:, Folder 2088)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 57:, Folder 2089)
      - International trade (Box 58:, Folder 2090-2093)
      - Latin America (Box 58:, Folder 2094-2095)
      - Middle East (Box 58:, Folder 2096-2097)
      - New Trade Pact (Box 58:, Folder 2098)
      - Steel Imports (Box 58:, Folder 2099-2100)
      - Soviet Union and Eastern Europe (Box 58:, Folder 2101)
      - United Nations (Box 58:, Folder 2102)
    - General Government
      - General (Box 58:, Folder 2103-2104)
      - Campaign Reform (Box 58:, Folder 2105)
    - General Government
      - Civil Defense (Box 58:, Folder 2106)
      - Communications (Box 58:, Folder 2107)
      - Constitutional Convention (Box 58:, Folder 2108)
      - Immigration Law (Box 58:, Folder 2109)
      - Issue Analysis (Box 58:, Folder 2110)
      - Lobby Reform (Box 58:, Folder 2111)
      - Public Employees (Box 58:, Folder 2112)
      - Public Works Legislation (Box 58:, Folder 2113)
      - Questionnaires (Box 58:, Folder 2114)
      - Regulatory Reform (Box 58:, Folder 2115)
      - Reorganization (Box 58:, Folder 2116)
      - Stockpile (Box 58:, Folder 2117)
      - Tri-State Planning Commission (Box 58:, Folder 2118)
    - Health and Safety
      - General (Box 58:, Folder 2119-2120)
      - Abortion (Box 59:, Folder 2121-2124)
      - Diseases (Box 59:, Folder 2125)
      - Drugs and Food Labeling (Box 59:, Folder 2126)
      - Health Manpower (Box 59:, Folder 2127)
      - Hospitals and Nursing homes (Box 59:, Folder 2128-2130)
      - Narcotics (Box 59:, Folder 2131)
      - National Health Insurance (Box 59:, Folder 2132)
      - Rehabilitation (Box 59:, Folder 2133)
      - Veterinary (Box 59:, Folder 2134)
    - House of Representatives/General
      - General (Box 59:, Folder 2135)
      - Tax Break (Box 59:, Folder 2136)
    - House of Representatives/In-House
      - Administrative Review Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2137)
      - Ball Bearing Caucus (Box 59:, Folder 2138)
      - Clearinghouse of the Future (Box 59:, Folder 2139)
      - Clearinghouse on Women's Rights (Box 59:, Folder 2140)
      - Campaign Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2141)
      - Committee Assignments (Box 59:, Folder 2142)
      - Select Committee on Committees (Box 59:, Folder 2143)
      - Computers (Box 59:, Folder 2144)
      - Democratic Caucus Rules and Rules Changes (Box 59:, Folder 2145-2146)
      - Democratic Organization Caucus (Box 59:, Folder 2147)
      - Democratic Steering and Policy Committee (Box 59:, Folder 2148)
      - Democratic Study Group and Meeting Notices (Box 59:, Folder 2149-2150)
      - Democratic Whip System (Box 59:, Folder 2151)
      - Environmental Study Conference (Box 59:, Folder 2152)
    - House of Representatives/In-House
      - House Rules (Box 59:, Folder 2153)
      - House Rules Changes (Box 59:, Folder 2154)
      - Irish Caucus (Box 59:, Folder 2155)
      - Italian American Caucus (Box 59:, Folder 2156)
      - Korean Lobbying (Box 60:, Folder 2157)
      - Leadership (Box 60:, Folder 2158)
      - Members of Congress for Peace Through Law (Box 60:, Folder 2159)
      - Miscellaneous Caucus (Box 60:, Folder 2160)
      - New England
        - Caucus (Box 60:, Folder 2161-2162)
        - Fuel Institution (Box 60:, Folder 2163)
        - Regional Commission (Box 60:, Folder 2164)
      - Northeast-Midwest Economic Coalition (Box 60:, Folder 2165-2168)
      - Pay Raises (Box 60:, Folder 2169)
      - Port Caucus (Box 60:, Folder 2170)
      - Reform (Box 60:, Folder 2171)
      - Rural Caucus (Box 60:, Folder 2172)
      - Steel Caucus (Box 60:, Folder 2173)
      - Suburban Caucus (Box 60:, Folder 2174)
      - Textile Caucus (Box 60:, Folder 2175)
      - Task Force on Taxation and Capital Formation (Box 60:, Folder 2176)
    - Housing and Urban Problems
      - General (Box 60:, Folder 2177-2178)
      - Community Development Act (Box 60:, Folder 2179)
      - Urban Policy Plan (Box 60:, Folder 2180)
    - Judiciary
      - General (Box 60:, Folder 2181)
      - Capital Punishment (Box 60:, Folder 2182)
      - Criminal Laws (Box 60:, Folder 2183)
      - Gun Control (Box 60:, Folder 2184)
      - LEAA (Box 60:, Folder 2185)
    - Labor
      - General (Box 60:, Folder 2186-2187)
      - Illegal Aliens (Box 60:, Folder 2188)
      - Manpower/Legislative Attitudes (Box 61:, Folder 2189)
      - Manpower (Box 61:, Folder 2190)
      - OSHA (Box 61:, Folder 2191)
      - Pensions (Box 61:, Folder 2192)
      - Right to Work (Box 61:, Folder 2193)
      - Unemployment Compensation (Box 61:, Folder 2194)
    - Postal Service
      - General (Box 61:, Folder 2195)
    - Postal Service
      - Commemorative Stamps (Box 61:, Folder 2196)
      - Postal Labor (Box 61:, Folder 2197)
    - Poverty Programs
      - General (Box 61:, Folder 2198)
      - Child Care (Box 61:, Folder 2199)
      - Food Stamps (Box 61:, Folder 2200)
      - Social Services (Box 61:, Folder 2201)
      - Welfare Reform (Box 61:, Folder 2202)
    - Social Security
      - General (Box 61:, Folder 2203)
      - Benefit Increases (Box 61:, Folder 2204)
      - Disability Benefits (Box 61:, Folder 2205)
      - Earnings Limitation (Box 61:, Folder 2206)
      - Eligibility (Box 61:, Folder 2207)
      - Medicare/Medicaid (Box 61:, Folder 2208)
      - Older Americans Programs (Box 61:, Folder 2209)
      - Payroll Tax (Box 61:, Folder 2210)
      - Railroad Retirement Benefits (Box 61:, Folder 2211)
      - Spouses Benefits (Box 61:, Folder 2212)
      - Universal Coverage (Box 61:, Folder 2213)
    - Taxation
      - General (Box 61:, Folder 2214)
      - Corporations and Special Interests (Box 61:, Folder 2215)
      - Income Tax, Individual (Box 61:, Folder 2216)
      - Reductions (Box 61:, Folder 2217)
      - Reform (Box 61:, Folder 2218)
      - Tax Credits (Box 61:, Folder 2219)
    - Transportation
      - General (Box 61:, Folder 2220)
      - AMTRAK-General (Box 61:, Folder 2221)
      - Aviation (Box 62:, Folder 2222)
      - Buses and Trucks (Box 62:, Folder 2223-2224)
      - Conrail-General (Box 62:, Folder 2225)
      - Highways (Box 62:, Folder 2226)
      - Mass Transit (Box 62:, Folder 2227)
      - No-Fault Insurance (Box 62:, Folder 2228)
      - Railroads
        - General (Box 62:, Folder 2229)
        - Northeast Corridor (Box 62:, Folder 2230)
      - Shipping (Box 62:, Folder 2231)
    - Veterans
      - General (Box 62:, Folder 2232)
    - Veterans
      - Disability (Box 62:, Folder 2233)
      - Education (Box 62:, Folder 2234)
      - Health (Box 62:, Folder 2235)
      - Pensions (Box 62:, Folder 2236)
  - 96th Congress, 2nd Session, 1980
    - Legislative File Index (Box 62:, Folder 2237)
    - General Legislation
      - State Matter/No Jurisdiction (Box 62:, Folder 2238)
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 62:, Folder 2239)
    - Animal Protection
      - General (Box 62:, Folder 2240)
      - Endangered Species Act (Box 62:, Folder 2241)
    - Arts and Humanities
      - General (Box 62:, Folder 2242)
    - Business
      - General (Box 62:, Folder 2243)
      - Banking and Finance (Box 62:, Folder 2244)
      - Business Legislative Attitudes (Box 62:, Folder 2245)
      - Chrysler (Box 62:, Folder 2246)
      - Independent Business Ballots (Box 62:, Folder 2247)
      - Product Liability (Box 62:, Folder 2248)
      - Small Business (Box 62:, Folder 2249)
    - Civil Rights and Liberties
      - General (Box 62:, Folder 2250)
      - Indian Affairs (Box 62:, Folder 2251)
      - School Busing (Box 62:, Folder 2252)
      - School Prayer (Box 62:, Folder 2253)
      - Women's Rights (Box 62:, Folder 2254)
    - Consumers (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 63:, Folder 2255)
      - CATV (Box 63:, Folder 2256)
      - Consumer Protection Legislation (Box 63:, Folder 2257)
      - Copyrights-Patents (Box 63:, Folder 2258)
      - Privacy (Box 63:, Folder 2259)
    - Economy
      - General (Box 63:, Folder 2260)
      - Debt Ceiling (Box 63:, Folder 2261)
      - Federal Spending (Box 63:, Folder 2262-2263)
      - Minimum Wage (Box 63:, Folder 2264)
      - Revenue Spending (Box 63:, Folder 2265)
      - Unemployment (Box 63:, Folder 2266)
    - Economy
      - Balanced Budget (Box 63:, Folder 2267)
    - Education
      - General (Box 63:, Folder 2268)
      - ESEA (Box 63:, Folder 2269)
      - Higher Education (Box 63:, Folder 2270)
      - Libraries/Support Services (Box 63:, Folder 2271)
      - Nutrition Programs (Box 63:, Folder 2272)
      - Vocational/Adult (Box 63:, Folder 2273)
    - Energy
      - General (Box 63:, Folder 2274)
      - Coal (Box 63:, Folder 2275)
      - Natural gas (Box 63:, Folder 2276)
      - Nuclear (Box 63:, Folder 2277)
      - Oil and Gasoline (Box 63:, Folder 2278-2279)
      - Research and Development (Box 63:, Folder 2280)
      - Solar/Geothermal (Box 63:, Folder 2281)
      - Synfuels (Box 63:, Folder 2282)
    - Environment
      - General (Box 63:, Folder 2283)
      - Air Pollution (Box 63:, Folder 2284)
      - Hazardous Waste (Box 63:, Folder 2285)
      - National Parks and Forests (Box 63:, Folder 2286)
      - Noise Pollution (Box 63:, Folder 2287)
      - Water Pollution (Box 63:, Folder 2288)
    - Foreign Affairs
      - General (Box 63:, Folder 2289)
      - Africa (Box 63:, Folder 2290)
      - Asia (Box 63:, Folder 2291)
      - Europe and NATO (Box 63:, Folder 2292)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 63:, Folder 2293)
      - International Trade (Box 63:, Folder 2294)
      - Iran (Box 64:, Folder 2295)
      - Israel (Box 64:, Folder 2296)
      - Latin America (Box 64:, Folder 2297)
      - Middle East (Box 64:, Folder 2298)
      - Steel Imports (Box 64:, Folder 2299)
      - Soviet Union and Eastern Europe (Box 64:, Folder 2300)
      - United Nations (Box 64:, Folder 2301)
    - General Government
      - General (Box 64:, Folder 2302)